{
    "subject": "resource/New_Order",
    "predicate": "ontology/genre",
    "object": "resource/New_wave_music",
    "human_readable": "New Order's genre is New wave music.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9472457766532898,
            "question": "What makes New Order's music stand out within the New wave genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8962976932525635,
            "question": "Besides New wave music, are there any other genres that influence New Order's sound?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8164739012718201,
            "question": "What musical genre is New Order associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7255879044532776,
            "question": "What type of music does New Order play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7097165584564209,
            "question": "How would you describe the style of New Order's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6931513547897339,
            "question": "Which music movement influenced New Order's sound?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.68654865026474,
            "question": "How has New Order's music influenced other artists?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6379573345184326,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a song by New Order that exemplifies their genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5760228037834167,
            "question": "What is New Order known for in the music world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5495798587799072,
            "question": "What is the legacy of New Order in the music industry?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=New Order's genre is New wave music.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6038_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is New Order known for in the music world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6038_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give an example of a song by New Order that exemplifies their genre?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6038_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has New Order's music influenced other artists?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6038_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6038_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6038_144.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6038_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6038_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6038_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6038_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6038_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6038_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6038_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6038_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide multiple references to New Order being categorized as a new wave band, which supports the statement that their genre is New Wave music."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}